{"transport":[{"level":"1","type":"transport","question":"I go on the road, and I have wheels. Toot toot!","hints":[{"text":"🚗 I help you travel from place to place."},{"text":"👨‍👩‍👧‍👦 I can carry your family."},{"text":"⛽️ I need gas to go."}],"options":[{"label":"Car","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Train","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Airplane","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","sound":"car_horn.mp3"}},{"level":"2","type":"transport","question":"I float on water and can be big or small.","hints":[{"text":"🌊 I travel on oceans and lakes."},{"text":"⚓️ I can have sails or an engine."},{"text":"🛥️ Pirates sometimes use me!"}],"options":[{"label":"Bike","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Boat","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bus","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","sound":"boat_horn.mp3"}},{"level":"3","type":"transport","question":"I fly in the sky and take people far away.","hints":[{"text":"☁️ I have wings."},{"text":"💺 You sit inside me to travel."},{"text":"✈️ I fly very high."}],"options":[{"label":"Airplane","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Scooter","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Tractor","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","sound":"airplane.mp3"}},{"level":"4","type":"transport","question":"I travel on tracks and carry lots of people.","hints":[{"text":"🛤️ I make a 'choo choo' sound."},{"text":"🚂 I have many carriages."},{"text":"⏱️ I run on a schedule."}],"options":[{"label":"Train","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Helicopter","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Skateboard","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","sound":"train.mp3"}},{"level":"5","type":"transport","question":"I have two wheels and you pedal to move me.","hints":[{"text":"🚲 You need to balance to ride me."},{"text":"🔔 I often have a bell."},{"text":"🚴 I am good exercise."}],"options":[{"label":"Bike","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Truck","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Hot Air Balloon","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","sound":"bike_bell.mp3"}},{"level":"6","type":"transport","question":"I am big and yellow and take kids to school.","hints":[{"text":"🛑 I have flashing lights when I stop."},{"text":"🎒 Many students ride on me."},{"text":"🚌 I am longer than a car."}],"options":[{"label":"Bus","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Taxi","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Motorbike","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","sound":"bus.mp3"}},{"level":"7","type":"transport","question":"I help build things on construction sites and have a big scoop.","hints":[{"text":"👷I dig and move dirt."},{"text":"🚧 I am often orange or yellow."},{"text":"🚜 I have a very strong engine."}],"options":[{"label":"Fire Truck","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Excavator","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Police Car","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","sound":"excavator.mp3"}},{"level":"8","type":"transport","question":"I have a siren and flashing lights and help people in emergencies.","hints":[{"text":"🚨I rush to accidents and fires."},{"text":"👨‍⚕️ I might take you to the hospital."},{"text":"🚑 I'm faster than a regular car."}],"options":[{"label":"Ambulance","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Garbage Truck","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Camper Van","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","sound":"ambulance.mp3"}},{"level":"9","type":"transport","question":"I carry things and can be very big. Sometimes I use a trailer","hints":[{"text":"📦I deliver packages."},{"text":"🚚 I have many wheels."},{"text":"⛽ I use a lot of fuel."}],"options":[{"label":"Truck","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Tuk-Tuk","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Minivan","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","sound":"truck.mp3"}},{"level":"10","type":"transport","question":"I have a seat for one person and two wheels, but I'm not a bicycle. I go fast!","hints":[{"text":"🛵 You need to wear a helmet to ride me."},{"text":"🚦 I have an engine."},{"text":"🛣️ I'm smaller than a car but faster than a bike."}],"options":[{"label":"Motorbike","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Trolley","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Segway","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍","sound":"motorbike.mp3"}}],"bug":[{"level":"1","type":"bug","question":"I have six legs and I like to crawl. Sometimes I tickle!","hints":[{"text":"🐜 I am very small and can be found on the ground"},{"text":"🧺 I often carry food much bigger than me back to my home"},{"text":"💪 I'm known for being very strong for my size"}],"options":[{"label":"Ant","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}},{"level":"2","type":"bug","question":"I can fly and I like to land on flowers to drink yummy juice.","hints":[{"text":"🌸 I like colourful places"},{"text":"🦋 I start as a caterpillar"},{"text":"🌈 You can see me in many colours"}],"options":[{"label":"Butterfly","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cat","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bear","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}},{"level":"3","type":"bug","question":"I make honey for you to eat. I live in a hive.","hints":[{"text":"🐝 I buzz around"},{"text":"🌻 I like to collect yellow dust from flowers"},{"text":"🍯 My home is full of sweet goo"}],"options":[{"label":"Bee","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Pig","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}},{"level":"4","type":"bug","question":"I jump very high and I'm green. I make a chirping sound.","hints":[{"text":"🌿 I am often found in grassy areas."},{"text":"🎵 I can be very noisy in the summer."},{"text":"🐸 Some animals like to eat me."}],"options":[{"label":"Grasshopper","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Turtle","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Rabbit","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}},{"level":"5","type":"bug","question":"I light up the night sky, like a tiny star.","hints":[{"text":"✨ I have a glow"},{"text":"💡 I use my light to attract a friend"},{"text":"🌙 You see me when it gets dark"}],"options":[{"label":"Firefly","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Ladybug","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Caterpillar","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}},{"level":"6","type":"bug","question":"I like to eat wood. Sometimes I make a house fall down!","hints":[{"text":"🪵 I am found where there is wood"},{"text":"🏠 People don't want me in their houses"},{"text":"🐜 I live in a colony and work together"}],"options":[{"label":"Termite","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Spider","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Snail","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}},{"level":"7","type":"bug","question":"I make a sticky web to catch my food.","hints":[{"text":"🕸️ I have eight legs."},{"text":"🕷️ I am not an insect."},{"text":"🦟 Flies are my favorite snack."}],"options":[{"label":"Spider","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Mosquito","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Beetle","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}},{"level":"8","type":"bug","question":"I am red, black, or yellow, and have spots on my back. People say I'm lucky.","hints":[{"text":"🐞 I am a small, round beetle"},{"text":"🌱 I like to eat aphids in gardens"},{"text":"🍀 Finding me is said to bring good fortune"}],"options":[{"label":"Ladybug","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Centipede","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Dragonfly","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}},{"level":"9","type":"bug","question":"I fly around at night and like to drink your blood. Ouch!","hints":[{"text":"🧛‍♀️ I am a pest"},{"text":"🦟 I make an itchy bite"},{"text":"🦇 Some people think I am like a tiny vampire"}],"options":[{"label":"Mosquito","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Housefly","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Earwig","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}},{"level":"10","type":"bug","question":"I have big eyes and transparent wings. I like to fly near water.","hints":[{"text":"🌊 I am often near rivers or lakes"},{"text":"👀 I have excellent vision"},{"text":"🚁 I dart around very quickly"}],"options":[{"label":"Dragonfly","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cricket","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Moth","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🐛"}}]}